(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, I think I've come up
with a fun way...
(Sheldon:)...to get young people
interested in science.
Physics Mad Libs.
(Sheldon:)Now, give me a number.
(Sheldon:)- Five.
- Uh-huh.
(Sheldon:)And an irrational constant.
(Scene:)E.
(Sheldon:)And a funny Greek letter.
- Gamma.
- I said funny.
- Upsilon?
- Heh, good one.
(Sheldon:)And an electrical charge.
- Positive.
- Ha, ha! Perfect.
Okay, get this. Ahem.
"Professor Jones
told the symposium...
(Sheldon:)...he had a new method
for calculating the mass of a muon.
Five times the limit of, heh...
...E to the upsilon as it approaches..."
Ha, ha, oh, my gosh. Okay.
Okay, no, no. Ahem.
(Sheldon:)I'll start over.
"Professor Jo..."
(Howard:)I haven't seen him laugh that hard...